[{"title": "General Knowledge (Cricket) Quiz (Hard)", "language": "Urdu", "difficulty": "Hard", "topic": "General Knowledge (Cricket)", "created_at": "2025-05-11 21:24:30", "questions": [{"question": "\u0633\u0631\u0641\u0631\u0627\u0632 \u0627\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0646\u06d2 \u06a9\u0648\u0646 \u0633\u06cc \u0679\u06cc\u0645 \u06a9\u06d2 \u0644\u0626\u06d2 \u0633\u0628 \u0633\u06d2 \u0632\u06cc\u0627\u062f\u06c1 \u0679\u06cc20 \u0628\u06cc\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0642\u0648\u0627\u0645\u06cc \u0645\u06cc\u0686\u0632 \u06a9\u06be\u06cc\u0644\u06d2 \u06c1\u06cc\u06ba\u061f", "answer": "\u067e\u0627\u06a9\u0633\u062a\u0627\u0646", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u067e\u0627\u06a9\u0633\u062a\u0627\u0646", "\u0628\u06be\u0627\u0631\u062a", "\u0622\u0633\u0679\u0631\u06cc\u0644\u06cc\u0627", "\u0627\u0646\u06af\u0644\u06cc\u0646\u0688"]}, {"question": "\u06a9\u0648\u0646 \u0633\u0627 \u06a9\u06be\u06cc\u0644 \u06a9\u0627 \u0645\u06cc\u062f\u0627\u0646 '\u06af\u0644\u0627\u0628\u06cc \u06af\u06cc\u0646\u062f' \u0679\u06cc\u0633\u0679 \u0645\u06cc\u0686 \u06a9\u06d2 \u0644\u0626\u06d2 \u0645\u0634\u06c1\u0648\u0631 \u06c1\u06d2\u061f", "answer": "\u0627\u06cc\u0688\u06cc\u0644\u06cc\u0688 \u0627\u0648\u0648\u0644", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0627\u06cc\u0688\u06cc\u0644\u06cc\u0688 \u0627\u0648\u0648\u0644", "\u0645\u06cc\u0644\u0628\u0648\u0631\u0646 \u06a9\u0631\u06a9\u0679 \u06af\u0631\u0627\u0624\u0646\u0688", "\u0644\u0627\u0631\u0688\u0632", "\u0633\u0688\u0646\u06cc \u06a9\u0631\u06a9\u0679 \u06af\u0631\u0627\u0624\u0646\u0688"]}, {"question": "\u06a9\u0648\u0646 \u0633\u0627 \u06a9\u06be\u0644\u0627\u0691\u06cc \u0627\u067e\u0646\u06d2 \u06a9\u06cc\u0631\u06cc\u0626\u0631 \u0645\u06cc\u06ba \u0633\u0628 \u0633\u06d2 \u0632\u06cc\u0627\u062f\u06c1 \u0686\u06be\u06a9\u06d2 \u0645\u0627\u0631\u0646\u06d2 \u06a9\u0627 \u0631\u06cc\u06a9\u0627\u0631\u0688 \u0631\u06a9\u06be\u062a\u0627 \u06c1\u06d2\u061f", "answer": "\u06a9\u0631\u0646\u0644 \u0627\u0631\u0628\u0627\u0632", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u06a9\u0631\u0646\u0644 \u0627\u0631\u0628\u0627\u0632", "\u0634\u0639\u06cc\u0628 \u0627\u062e\u062a\u0631", "\u0631\u0624\u0641 \u06cc\u0627\u0633\u0631", "\u0628\u0646\u062f\u0631 \u062d\u06cc\u0631\u062a"]}, {"question": "\u062f\u0648\u0631\u06c1 \u067e\u0627\u06a9\u0633\u062a\u0627\u0646 \u06a9\u06d2 \u062f\u0648\u0631\u0627\u0646 \u06a9\u062a\u0646\u06d2 \u0645\u0644\u06a9\u0648\u06ba \u06a9\u06cc \u0679\u06cc\u0645\u06cc\u06ba 2019 \u0645\u06cc\u06ba \u0622\u0626\u06cc \u062a\u06be\u06cc\u06ba\u061f", "answer": "5", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["3", "5", "7", "9"]}, {"question": "\u06a9\u0633 \u06a9\u06be\u0644\u0627\u0691\u06cc \u0646\u06d2 2007 \u06a9\u06d2 \u0648\u0631\u0644\u0688 \u0679\u06cc20 \u06a9\u0627 \u0641\u0627\u0626\u0646\u0644 \u062c\u06cc\u062a\u0646\u06d2 \u06a9\u06d2 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u06af\u0632\u0631\u06d2 10 \u0633\u0627\u0644\u0648\u06ba \u0645\u06cc\u06ba \u0645\u062a\u0639\u062f\u062f \u0627\u0646\u0641\u0631\u0627\u062f\u06cc \u0627\u06cc\u0648\u0627\u0631\u0688\u0632 \u062d\u0627\u0635\u0644 \u06a9\u06cc\u06d2\u061f", "answer": "\u06cc\u0648\u0633\u0641 \u06cc\u0648\u062d\u0646\u0627", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u06cc\u0648\u0633\u0641 \u06cc\u0648\u062d\u0646\u0627", "\u0628\u06c1\u0627\u0631\u06cc \u0627\u0642\u0628\u0627\u0644", "\u0639\u0645\u0631 \u0627\u06a9\u0645\u0644", "\u0634\u0627\u06c1\u062f \u0622\u0641\u0631\u06cc\u062f\u06cc"]}, {"question": "\u06a9\u0648\u0646 \u0633\u06cc \u0679\u06cc\u0633\u0679 \u0633\u06cc\u0631\u06cc\u0632 \u0645\u06cc\u06ba \u067e\u06c1\u0644\u06cc \u0628\u0627\u0631 \u0646\u0626\u06cc \u06af\u06cc\u0646\u062f \u06a9\u0627 \u0627\u0633\u062a\u0639\u0645\u0627\u0644 \u06a9\u06cc\u0627 \u06af\u06cc\u0627 \u062a\u06be\u0627\u061f", "answer": "1877", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["1877", "1888", "1905", "1947"]}, {"question": "\u06a9\u0648\u0646 \u0633\u0627 \u0642\u0648\u0645\u06cc \u06a9\u0631\u06a9\u0679 \u0628\u0648\u0631\u0688 \u062f\u0646\u06cc\u0627 \u06a9\u0627 \u0633\u0628 \u0633\u06d2 \u0642\u062f\u06cc\u0645 \u06a9\u0631\u06a9\u0679 \u0628\u0648\u0631\u0688 \u0645\u0627\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0627\u062a\u0627 \u06c1\u06d2\u061f", "answer": "\u0627\u0646\u06af\u0644\u06cc\u0646\u0688", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0627\u0646\u06af\u0644\u06cc\u0646\u0688", "\u0622\u0633\u0679\u0631\u06cc\u0644\u06cc\u0627", "\u0628\u06be\u0627\u0631\u062a", "\u062c\u0646\u0648\u0628\u06cc \u0627\u0641\u0631\u06cc\u0642\u06c1"]}, {"question": "\u0633\u0628 \u0633\u06d2 \u0632\u06cc\u0627\u062f\u06c1 \u0648\u0646 \u0688\u06d2 \u0627\u0646\u0679\u0631\u0646\u06cc\u0634\u0646\u0644 \u0645\u06cc\u0686\u0632 \u0645\u06cc\u06ba \u0634\u0631\u06a9\u062a \u06a9\u0631\u0646\u06d2 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0627 \u06a9\u06be\u0644\u0627\u0691\u06cc \u06a9\u0648\u0646 \u06c1\u06d2\u061f", "answer": "\u0633\u0686\u0646 \u0679\u0646\u0688\u0648\u0644\u06a9\u0631", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0633\u0686\u0646 \u0679\u0646\u0688\u0648\u0644\u06a9\u0631", "\u0688\u06cc\u0631\u06a9 \u0645\u0648\u0631\u06cc\u0633", "\u062c\u06d2 \u0688\u06cc \u0631\u0686\u0627\u0631\u062f\u0633\u0646", "\u0628\u0631\u0627\u0626\u0646 \u0644\u0627\u0631\u0627"]}, {"question": "\u0622\u062e\u0631\u06cc \u0628\u0627\u0631 2021 \u0645\u06cc\u06ba \u06a9\u0648\u0646 \u0633\u06d2 \u0648\u0631\u0644\u0688 \u06a9\u067e \u0679\u0648\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u0646\u0679 \u06a9\u06d2 \u0627\u0646\u0639\u0642\u0627\u062f \u06a9\u06d2 \u0628\u0639\u062f \u06a9\u06be\u06cc\u0644\u06d2 \u06af\u0626\u06d2\u061f", "answer": "\u0679\u06cc20 \u0648\u0631\u0644\u0688 \u06a9\u067e", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0679\u06cc20 \u0648\u0631\u0644\u0688 \u06a9\u067e", "\u0648\u0646 \u0688\u06d2 \u0648\u0631\u0644\u0688 \u06a9\u067e", "\u0627\u0646\u0688\u0631 19 \u0648\u0631\u0644\u0688 \u06a9\u067e", "\u0641\u06cc\u0641\u0627 \u0648\u0631\u0644\u0688 \u06a9\u067e"]}, {"question": "\u06a9\u0648\u0646 \u0633\u06cc \u0645\u06c1\u0627\u0631\u062a \u06a9\u0631\u06a9\u0679 \u06a9\u06d2 \u06a9\u06be\u06cc\u0644 \u0645\u06cc\u06ba '\u0688\u06a9' \u06a9\u06c1\u0644\u0627\u062a\u06cc \u06c1\u06d2\u061f", "answer": "\u06a9\u06be\u0644\u0627\u0691\u06cc \u06a9\u0627 \u0628\u063a\u06cc\u0631 \u0631\u0646 \u0628\u0646\u0627\u0626\u06d2 \u0622\u0624\u0679 \u06c1\u0648\u0646\u0627", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u06a9\u06be\u0644\u0627\u0691\u06cc \u06a9\u0627 \u0628\u063a\u06cc\u0631 \u0631\u0646 \u0628\u0646\u0627\u0626\u06d2 \u0622\u0624\u0679 \u06c1\u0648\u0646\u0627", "\u06a9\u06be\u0644\u0627\u0691\u06cc \u06a9\u0627 \u0627\u06cc\u06a9 \u0627\u0648\u0648\u0631 \u0645\u06cc\u06ba \u06a9\u0626\u06cc \u0631\u0646 \u0628\u0646\u0627\u0646\u0627", "\u06a9\u06be\u0644\u0627\u0691\u06cc \u06a9\u0627 \u06af\u06cc\u0646\u062f \u06a9\u0648 \u0686\u06be\u06a9\u06d2 \u067e\u0631 \u0645\u0627\u0631\u0646\u0627", "\u06a9\u06be\u0644\u0627\u0691\u06cc \u06a9\u0627 \u06af\u06cc\u0646\u062f \u06a9\u0648 \u0628\u0627\u0624\u0646\u0688\u0631\u06cc \u06a9\u06d2 \u0628\u0627\u06c1\u0631 \u067e\u06be\u06cc\u0646\u06a9\u0646\u0627"]}], "id": "1_20250511212430"}, {"title": "General Knowledge (cricket) Quiz (Hard)", "language": "Telugu", "difficulty": "Hard", "topic": "General Knowledge (cricket)", "created_at": "2025-05-11 21:27:04", "questions": [{"question": "\u0c05\u0c02\u0c24\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c1c\u0c3e\u0c24\u0c40\u0c2f \u0c15\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d\u200c\u0c15\u0c41 \u0c38\u0c02\u0c2c\u0c02\u0c27\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c1a\u0c3f, '\u0c1f\u0c46\u0c38\u0c4d\u0c1f\u0c4d \u0c15\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d'\u0c32\u0c4b \u0c2e\u0c42\u0c21\u0c35 \u0c07\u0c28\u0c4d\u0c28\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c17\u0c4d\u0c38\u0c4d \u0c15\u0c4b\u0c38\u0c02 \u0c0e\u0c02\u0c24 \u0c38\u0c2e\u0c2f\u0c02 \u0c2b\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c4d\u0c38\u0c4d \u0c1a\u0c47\u0c2f\u0c2c\u0c21\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c26\u0c3f?", "answer": "90 \u0c28\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c37\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c41", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["120 \u0c28\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c37\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c41", "90 \u0c28\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c37\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c41", "75 \u0c28\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c37\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c41", "60 \u0c28\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c37\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c41"]}, {"question": "\u0c2a\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c2a\u0c02\u0c1a\u0c15\u0c2a\u0c4d\u200c\u0c32\u0c4b \u0c05\u0c24\u0c4d\u0c2f\u0c27\u0c3f\u0c15 \u0c36\u0c24\u0c15\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c28\u0c41 \u0c38\u0c3e\u0c27\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c1a\u0c3f\u0c28 \u0c15\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c30\u0c4d \u0c0e\u0c35\u0c30\u0c41?", "answer": "\u0c38\u0c1a\u0c3f\u0c28\u0c4d \u0c1f\u0c46\u0c02\u0c21\u0c42\u0c32\u0c4d\u0c15\u0c30\u0c4d", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0c14\u0c09\u0c28\u0c4d \u0c2e\u0c4b\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c28\u0c40", "\u0c2c\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c46\u0c02\u0c21\u0c4d \u0c39\u0c4b\u0c2a\u0c4d", "\u0c38\u0c1a\u0c3f\u0c28\u0c4d \u0c1f\u0c46\u0c02\u0c21\u0c42\u0c32\u0c4d\u0c15\u0c30\u0c4d", "\u0c26\u0c3f\u0c28\u0c47\u0c37\u0c4d \u0c15\u0c3e\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c24\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c4d"]}, {"question": "\u0c10\u0c38\u0c40\u0c38\u0c40 \u0c1c\u0c3e\u0c24\u0c40\u0c2f \u0c24\u0c3e\u0c30\u0c3e\u0c17\u0c23\u0c02\u0c32\u0c4b \u0c28\u0c02\u0c2c\u0c30\u0c4d 1 \u0c38\u0c4d\u0c25\u0c3e\u0c28\u0c02 \u0c28\u0c41\u0c02\u0c21\u0c3f \u0c15\u0c28\u0c3f \u0c2a\u0c4b\u0c2f\u0c3f\u0c28 \u0c24\u0c4a\u0c32\u0c3f\u0c38\u0c3e\u0c30\u0c3f \u0c0e\u0c35\u0c30\u0c41?", "answer": "\u0c2a\u0c47\u0c26\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c4d\u0c15\u0c4d \u0c30\u0c3e\u0c39\u0c41\u0c32\u0c4d", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0c38\u0c4c\u0c30\u0c35\u0c4d \u0c17\u0c02\u0c17\u0c42\u0c32\u0c40", "\u0c2a\u0c47\u0c15\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c4d\u0c15\u0c4d \u0c30\u0c3e\u0c39\u0c41\u0c32\u0c4d", "\u0c2d\u0c41\u0c35\u0c28\u0c47\u0c36\u0c4d\u0c35\u0c30\u0c4d \u0c15\u0c41\u0c2e\u0c3e\u0c30\u0c4d", "\u0c35\u0c3f\u0c30\u0c3e\u0c1f\u0c4d \u0c15\u0c4b\u0c39\u0c4d\u0c32\u0c40"]}, {"question": "\u0c15\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d\u200c\u0c32\u0c4b '\u0c2f\u0c3e\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c21\u0c4d' \u0c2e\u0c30\u0c3f\u0c2f\u0c41 '\u0c2a\u0c47\u0c38\u0c4d' \u0c05\u0c28\u0c47 \u0c2a\u0c26\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c41 \u0c0f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c1f\u0c3f?", "answer": "\u0c2b\u0c40\u0c32\u0c4d\u0c21\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c17\u0c4d \u0c35\u0c4d\u0c2f\u0c35\u0c38\u0c4d\u0c25\u0c32\u0c41", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0c2c\u0c02\u0c24\u0c3f \u0c35\u0c47\u0c2f\u0c21\u0c02", "\u0c2b\u0c40\u0c32\u0c4d\u0c21\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c17\u0c4d \u0c35\u0c4d\u0c2f\u0c35\u0c38\u0c4d\u0c25\u0c32\u0c41", "\u0c2c\u0c4d\u0c2f\u0c3e\u0c1f\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c17\u0c4d \u0c2a\u0c26\u0c4d\u0c27\u0c24\u0c41\u0c32\u0c41", "\u0c30\u0c28\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c17\u0c4d \u0c38\u0c4d\u0c1f\u0c2f\u0c3f\u0c32\u0c4d\u0c38\u0c4d"]}, {"question": "\u0c24\u0c28 \u0c2b\u0c38\u0c4d\u0c1f\u0c4d \u0c15\u0c4d\u0c32\u0c3e\u0c38\u0c4d \u0c15\u0c46\u0c30\u0c40\u0c30\u0c4d\u200c\u0c32\u0c4b \u0c05\u0c24\u0c4d\u0c2f\u0c27\u0c3f\u0c15 \u0c36\u0c24\u0c15\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c28\u0c41 \u0c38\u0c3e\u0c27\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c1a\u0c3f\u0c28 \u0c06\u0c1f\u0c17\u0c3e\u0c21\u0c41 \u0c0e\u0c35\u0c30\u0c41?", "answer": "\u0c38\u0c1a\u0c3f\u0c28\u0c4d \u0c1f\u0c46\u0c02\u0c21\u0c42\u0c32\u0c4d\u0c15\u0c30\u0c4d", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0c30\u0c46\u0c3e\u0c17\u0c3e", "\u0c38\u0c1a\u0c3f\u0c28\u0c4d \u0c1f\u0c46\u0c02\u0c21\u0c42\u0c32\u0c4d\u0c15\u0c30\u0c4d", "\u0c2e\u0c48\u0c16\u0c47\u0c32\u0c4d \u0c35\u0c3e\u0c28\u0c4d", "\u0c32\u0c3e\u0c30\u0c46\u0c28\u0c4d \u0c38\u0c02\u0c18\u0c3f"]}, {"question": "\u0c2a\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c2a\u0c02\u0c1a\u0c15\u0c2a\u0c4d 2019\u0c32\u0c4b \u0c2b\u0c48\u0c28\u0c32\u0c4d \u0c2e\u0c4d\u0c2f\u0c3e\u0c1a\u0c4d\u200c\u0c32\u0c4b \u0c0f \u0c1c\u0c1f\u0c4d\u0c1f\u0c41 \u0c35\u0c3f\u0c1c\u0c2f\u0c02 \u0c38\u0c3e\u0c27\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c1a\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c26\u0c3f?", "answer": "\u0c07\u0c02\u0c17\u0c4d\u0c32\u0c3e\u0c02\u0c21\u0c4d", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0c06\u0c38\u0c4d\u0c1f\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c47\u0c32\u0c3f\u0c2f\u0c3e", "\u0c07\u0c02\u0c17\u0c4d\u0c32\u0c3e\u0c02\u0c21\u0c4d", "\u0c28\u0c4d\u0c2f\u0c42\u0c1c\u0c3f\u0c32\u0c3e\u0c02\u0c21\u0c4d", "\u0c2d\u0c3e\u0c30\u0c24\u0c26\u0c47\u0c36\u0c02"]}, {"question": "\u0c38\u0c2e\u0c15\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c40\u0c28 \u0c15\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d\u200c\u0c32\u0c4b \u0c05\u0c24\u0c4d\u0c2f\u0c02\u0c24 \u0c2a\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c2f\u0c4b\u0c1c\u0c28\u0c15\u0c30\u0c2e\u0c48\u0c28 \u0c2c\u0c4d\u0c2f\u0c3e\u0c1f\u0c4d\u0c38\u0c4d\u200c\u0c2e\u0c46\u0c28\u0c4d \u0c0e\u0c35\u0c30\u0c41?", "answer": "\u0c35\u0c3f\u0c30\u0c3e\u0c1f\u0c4d \u0c15\u0c4b\u0c39\u0c4d\u0c32\u0c40", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0c38\u0c1a\u0c3f\u0c28\u0c4d \u0c1f\u0c46\u0c02\u0c21\u0c42\u0c32\u0c4d\u0c15\u0c30\u0c4d", "\u0c30\u0c4b\u0c39\u0c3f\u0c24\u0c4d \u0c36\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c2e", "\u0c35\u0c3f\u0c30\u0c3e\u0c1f\u0c4d \u0c15\u0c4b\u0c39\u0c4d\u0c32\u0c40", "\u0c15\u0c47\u0c33\u0c4d \u0c30\u0c3e\u0c39\u0c41\u0c32\u0c4d"]}, {"question": "\u0c0f \u0c16\u0c4d\u0c2f\u0c3e\u0c24\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c2f\u0c02 \u0c15\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d \u0c2a\u0c1f\u0c4d\u0c32 '\u0c1a\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c3e \u0c35\u0c47\u0c17\u0c02\u0c17\u0c3e \u0c2c\u0c02\u0c24\u0c3f \u0c35\u0c47\u0c38\u0c4d\u0c24\u0c3e\u0c21\u0c41' \u0c05\u0c28\u0c3f \u0c17\u0c41\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c24\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c1a\u0c2c\u0c21\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c26\u0c3f?", "answer": "\u0c2c\u0c4b\u0c32\u0c4d \u0c38\u0c4d\u0c1f\u0c3e\u0c30\u0c4d \u0c2f\u0c3e\u0c2c\u0c4d", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0c35\u0c38\u0c40\u0c2e\u0c4d \u0c05\u0c15\u0c4d\u0c2e\u0c30\u0c4d", "\u0c2c\u0c4b\u0c32\u0c4d \u0c38\u0c4d\u0c1f\u0c3e\u0c30\u0c4d \u0c2f\u0c3e\u0c2c\u0c4d", "\u0c2c\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d \u0c32\u0c40", "\u0c36\u0c3e\u0c28\u0c40 \u0c39\u0c3e\u0c38\u0c28\u0c4d"]}, {"question": "\u0c15\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d\u200c\u0c32\u0c4b \u0c30\u0c28\u0c4d \u0c05\u0c35\u0c41\u0c1f\u0c4d \u0c38\u0c2e\u0c2f\u0c02\u0c32\u0c4b \u0c06\u0c1f\u0c17\u0c3e\u0c21\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c3f \u0c05\u0c02\u0c26\u0c41\u0c2c\u0c3e\u0c1f\u0c41\u0c32\u0c4b \u0c09\u0c28\u0c4d\u0c28 \u0c0e\u0c02\u0c24 \u0c38\u0c2e\u0c2f\u0c02 \u0c09\u0c02\u0c1f\u0c41\u0c02\u0c26\u0c3f?", "answer": "5 \u0c28\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c37\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c41", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["10 \u0c28\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c37\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c41", "5 \u0c28\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c37\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c41", "2 \u0c28\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c37\u0c3e\u0c32\u0c41", "1 \u0c28\u0c3f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c37\u0c02"]}, {"question": "\u0c15\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d\u200c\u0c32\u0c4b '\u0c38\u0c4d\u0c32\u0c3f\u0c2a\u0c4d' \u0c2b\u0c40\u0c32\u0c4d\u0c21\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c17\u0c4d \u0c2f\u0c4a\u0c15\u0c4d\u0c15 \u0c2a\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c3e\u0c27\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c15 \u0c09\u0c26\u0c4d\u0c26\u0c47\u0c36\u0c02 \u0c0f\u0c2e\u0c3f\u0c1f\u0c3f?", "answer": "\u0c2c\u0c4c\u0c32\u0c30\u0c4d \u0c2f\u0c4a\u0c15\u0c4d\u0c15 \u0c2c\u0c02\u0c24\u0c3f \u0c35\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d\u200c\u0c15\u0c41 \u0c1a\u0c47\u0c30\u0c21\u0c02", "type": "multiple_choice", "options": ["\u0c35\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d \u0c15\u0c3e\u0c2a\u0c32\u0c3e", "\u0c2c\u0c4c\u0c32\u0c30\u0c4d \u0c2f\u0c4a\u0c15\u0c4d\u0c15 \u0c2c\u0c02\u0c24\u0c3f \u0c35\u0c3f\u0c15\u0c46\u0c1f\u0c4d\u200c\u0c15\u0c41 \u0c1a\u0c47\u0c30\u0c21\u0c02", "\u0c12\u0c15 \u0c38\u0c4d\u0c1f\u0c4d\u0c30\u0c46\u0c2f\u0c3f\u0c1f\u0c4d \u0c2c\u0c02\u0c24\u0c3f\u0c28\u0c3f \u0c05\u0c21\u0c4d\u0c21\u0c41\u0c15\u0c4b\u0c35\u0c21\u0c02", "\u0c2c\u0c02\u0c24\u0c3f\u0c28\u0c3f \u0c2b\u0c40\u0c32\u0c4d\u0c21\u0c4d\u200c\u0c15\u0c3f \u0c2a\u0c02\u0c2a\u0c3f\u0c02\u0c1a\u0c21\u0c02"]}], "id": "2_20250511212704"}, {"title": "Generative AI Quiz (Easy)", "language": "English", "difficulty": "Easy", "topic": "Generative AI", "created_at": "2025-05-11 21:29:42", "questions": [{"question": "Generative AI can create text, images, and music.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Generative AI refers to algorithms that can generate diverse types of content, including text, visuals, and audio."}, {"question": "Generative AI is only used for creating visual art.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Generative AI is versatile and can be applied to various fields, not just visual art."}, {"question": "The output of Generative AI models is always original and never based on existing data.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Generative AI learns from existing datasets to create new outputs, which may resemble the input data."}, {"question": "OpenAI's GPT-3 is an example of a generative AI model.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "GPT-3 is designed to generate human-like text based on prompts."}, {"question": "Generative AI can be used in video game development.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "It is utilized to create assets, characters, and narratives in video games."}, {"question": "All generative AI models can produce multimedia outputs at the same quality.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Different models have varying strengths and weaknesses depending on their training and architecture."}, {"question": "Generative AI requires human intervention for every creative task.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "While human oversight is valuable, generative AI can autonomously produce content based on its training."}, {"question": "Generative adversarial networks (GANs) are a type of generative AI.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "GANs consist of two neural networks that work against each other to generate high-quality content."}, {"question": "Generative AI can assist in drug discovery by generating molecular structures.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Generative AI can be applied in various scientific fields, including pharmaceuticals, to facilitate research."}, {"question": "Generative AI is a newly invented technology with no prior research.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Generative AI builds upon decades of research in machine learning and artificial intelligence."}], "id": "3_20250511212942"}, {"title": "GEN AI Quiz (Hard)", "language": "English", "difficulty": "Hard", "topic": "GEN AI", "created_at": "2025-05-11 21:31:16", "questions": [{"question": "Generative AI can create entirely new concepts and ideas without any human input.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Generative AI typically relies on existing data and patterns to generate new content, meaning human input is often necessary."}, {"question": "The use of Generative AI is ethically uncontroversial and universally accepted in all fields.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Generative AI raises ethical concerns such as misinformation, copyright issues, and biases, leading to debates about its use."}, {"question": "Generative AI can only produce textual outputs and cannot be used for images or other media.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Generative AI is capable of producing various types of media, including images, audio, and video, beyond just text."}, {"question": "Deep learning models, which are commonly used in Generative AI, require vast amounts of training data.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Deep learning models rely on large datasets to learn patterns and make predictions effectively."}, {"question": "Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) consist of two components: a generator and a discriminator.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "GANs are comprised of these two components that compete against each other to improve the quality of generated data."}, {"question": "All forms of Generative AI output are guaranteed to be free from bias and inaccuracies.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Generative AI can perpetuate biases present in training data and may generate inaccurate information based on those biases."}, {"question": "The term 'deepfake' refers exclusively to audio manipulation using Generative AI.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Deepfakes can manipulate both video and audio to create realistic but fabricated content, not limited to audio."}, {"question": "Natural Language Processing (NLP) is a critical component of many Generative AI applications.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "NLP techniques are essential for understanding and generating human language in various Generative AI applications."}, {"question": "Generative AI models can operate independently of human intervention once trained, delivering consistent outputs.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "While they can function autonomously, human oversight is often required to refine and validate outputs."}, {"question": "All AI-generated content must be clearly labeled to avoid confusion with human-created content in order to adhere to ethical standards.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Transparency in labeling AI-generated content is crucial for ethical considerations and public trust."}], "id": "4_20250511213116"}, {"title": "AI Quiz (Hard)", "language": "English", "difficulty": "Hard", "topic": "AI", "created_at": "2025-05-11 21:33:25", "questions": [{"question": "Artificial Intelligence can fully replicate human emotions and consciousness.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "While AI can simulate emotional responses, it does not possess true consciousness or emotions."}, {"question": "Machine Learning is a subset of Artificial Intelligence that focuses on algorithms improving through experience.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Machine Learning involves algorithms that learn from data to improve performance over time."}, {"question": "The Turing Test is used to measure a machine's ability to exhibit intelligent behavior equivalent to, or indistinguishable from, that of a human.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "The Turing Test assesses whether a machine can mimic human responses well enough to be mistaken for a human."}, {"question": "Neural networks are designed to operate exclusively in structured data environments.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Neural networks can process both structured and unstructured data, making them versatile for various applications."}, {"question": "AI systems can make decisions without human intervention in all scenarios.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "AI can assist with decision-making but often requires human oversight, especially in complex situations."}, {"question": "Deep learning is a type of machine learning that uses multi-layered neural networks.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Deep learning employs deep neural networks to model complex patterns in large datasets."}, {"question": "Natural Language Processing (NLP) enables computers to understand and interpret human language.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "NLP is a branch of AI focused on the interaction between computers and humans through natural language."}, {"question": "Reinforcement learning is based solely on supervised learning techniques.", "answer": false, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Reinforcement learning involves learning by trial and error, utilizing rewards and punishments rather than supervised labels."}, {"question": "The concept of artificial neurons in an ANN (Artificial Neural Network) is directly inspired by biological neurons.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Artificial neurons mimic the function of biological neurons in processing information."}, {"question": "Expert systems in AI were developed to mimic human expertise in specific domains and require extensive knowledge bases.", "answer": true, "type": "true_false", "options": ["True", "False"], "explanation": "Expert systems are designed to solve complex problems by emulating the decision-making ability of a human expert."}], "id": "5_20250511213325"}]